I've always seen social media as a crowded
room.
Yeah.
Where
a podcast is where we sat together,
driving somewhere for three hours.
Let's talk, let's relax,
let the conversation wander.
But on Instagram, on TikTok, whatever,
I have 10 seconds to
capture your attention.
And I love the idea of polarizing people.
I said in my first book
that imagine you invite me
to a barbecue in Shoreditch,
and someone talks about Formula 1,
and I go,
"I fucking hate Formula 1." Someone goes,
"What?" I go, "Look, it just doesn't
interest me." And someone's like,
"You brought him the first time, and he's
shitting on Formula
1." 10 people at the barbecue,
three of them will be like,
"Do you know what?
I also agree with you.
I think it's shit."
And they'll remember me for saying
something controversial rather than, "Oh,
yeah, it's good, isn't it?
Oh, Lewis Hamilton, yeah." So
many people want to get in line with an
opinion that they're no longer remembered.
So I took it upon myself, and it
was almost by accident.
I do my Lives every day. I do videos.
Then something would piss me off,
and I'm not a violent person, so I'd just
channel it into a video,
and it would get a lot more likes
and shares.
And I was like, "Hold on.
What's going on here?"
Mm.
So again, I would post 10 videos,
and it would be the one where I
was a bit more
aggressive. And over time, I
learnt that there
were certain things people wanted in a
certain
way.
And it wasn't the six-packs,
the chicken and broccoli, the food prep.
It was being passionate without compromise
about different topics.
And
I do swear as a person. I am crass,
I am vulgar, and I do make
very inappropriate analogies for things.
I put that out.
Like I said,
I only ever wanted 10 clients.
So if half the people
that see a video hate me for it,
that's fine, because
as long as the other half
is 10 people that would do business with
me, again, I'm
invincible. And I've always had
that mentality that
I only need 10 people like me to make a
living.
And if I do those 30 hours at 150 pounds
an hour, six
hours between 6:00 a.m. and 2:00 p.m.,
I can live a dream life and be wealthy,
even though it's barely breaking 100 to
200K a year.
As long as I can buy dinner for my friends
and family, I can be wealthy with 10
people.
And people completely misconstrue social
media for that. They go,
"I need everyone to like me.
I need a million people to like me."
I first flew first class with 28,000
followers,
and you don't need
that many people to like you to do well.
And I wish people could understand
that because social media's become
a popularity contest. This
is not a popularity contest.
This is
a means of you getting people over the
line to like you enough to do business
with
you.